Okay. So you know how nonprofits are a fraud? Yes.
In what way do you mean it?
Well, namely because in majority of cases, they can't exist without the problem subsisting, right?
So they don't oftentimes actually seek to solve the problem because once that problem is solved, then there's no use for them.
So, I mean, there are many other ways that they are fraudulent, but that is one.
That is what you're describing.
Like, if you solve it, if you solve the issue of the two sides, et cetera, et cetera, of the lesser of two evils, then you actually have to do something.
Then something actually has to happen.
You end up removing an entire crux of folks who have built their whole existence on trying to find another.
And we are in a time, again, and I will say this again, I do not believe that any truly leftist candidate is genuinely trying to win.
Because there's no way to be a leftist in the Senate, in Congress, or in the president, or as the president or in his cabinet.
There is no way to do that in the current existence of the United States.
It is completely counterintuitive, counterrevolutionary.
And again, well, not again, because I didn't say this before, but the United States is not sovereign.
And that's the biggest lie.
It's folks acting like this is some, you know, place that's making decisions on its own.
And, you know, that Trump is sitting somewhere at night getting inspiration during his REM sleep and then waking up and saying, we're going to do this thing.
Like, that's not, that's just not the reality of where we are.
And until we are willing to actually address that reality, we're going to keep talking in circles because we're going to keep pruning branches instead of getting to the root.
And the root is, is that the United States and this whole electoral process that we have really, really, like, sunk our teeth into and, you know, really committed ourselves to changing is actually not the true problem.
That is the thing that's put in front of us.
The true problem is the world banking system and the IMF.
This is a global issue.
The United States is just, not just, but the United States has been used in the same way that England was used to be a colonizer.
And Israel has been its laboratory in order to create the weapons that continue to fund the ways in which these control systems go.
And until we actually connect the dots outside of here, we're just, we're just keeping ourselves entertained.
It's just, instead of doing the bread and circuses with football, we're doing the bread and circuses with politics.
And I know that because these people be fucking performing.
I was an actress.
I am an actress.
I know a performer when I see one.
And listen, J.D. Vance deserves a SAG award.